<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>maldives on Lessonfuse</title>
    <link>https://lessonfuse.com/blog/tags/maldives/</link>
    <description>Recent content in maldives on Lessonfuse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 18:05:55 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lessonfuse.com/blog/tags/maldives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Addressing the Teacher Shortage in Maldives: A Call for Local Educators</title>
      <link>https://lessonfuse.com/blog/posts/teacher-shortage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 18:05:55 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lessonfuse.com/blog/posts/teacher-shortage/</guid>
      <description>Maldivian schools follow the globally recognized Cambridge curriculum, emphasizing a high standard of education. However, the dearth of qualified teachers, especially those proficient in English, hampers the effective implementation of this curriculum. Recognizing the importance of local educators who possess a deep understanding of the Maldivian culture and context, the Ministry of Education has been working diligently to address this issue.
Over the past five years, there has been a steady increase in the number of Maldivian teachers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Education Challenges in the Maldives: Progress and Initiatives</title>
      <link>https://lessonfuse.com/blog/posts/educational-challanges-maldives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 18:05:55 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lessonfuse.com/blog/posts/educational-challanges-maldives/</guid>
      <description>Low Enrollment and Remarkable Progress When UNICEF arrived in the Maldives, only 15 percent of children were enrolled in primary schools. This low enrollment rate posed a significant challenge for the education sector. However, through collaborative efforts, the Maldives has witnessed a remarkable improvement in primary school enrollment, which now stands at an impressive 96 percent. This achievement is a testament to the commitment of the government and various organizations in ensuring that every child has access to education.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
